ADESINA, ADEDEJI SUNDAY

Road A, Number 17, Akinfenwa Street off Hope road, old-Ife road Ibadan, Oyo state. 09050731448, 07068923440. | adesinaadedeji8@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Result driven and efficient administrator with a least 3 years of administrative plus supervisory working experiences and a record of working to very high standards both with profit and non-profit making organizations. Holds a positive attitude to professional development. Excels in collaboration, team managment and possesses a proven record of inspiring others to achieve results. Manages duties effectively, and is able to resolve difficult customer and administrative situations. Seeking a challenging Administrative and Executive Assistant role as a career. Helping the organization to achieve results and aswell gain more experiences and skills.

WORK EXPERIENCES

• The Lord's International Schools. Sagamu, Ogun state.

2019 - 2020

Teacher

Served as a Corps member(NYSC) in the aforementioned school, impacting knowledge into students.

JLan Music Studio. Akure, Ondo State.

2018 - 2019

Manager

Worked as the Manager of the music studio, overseeing the activities of the organiziation and ensure its runnings.

• Chi Farms Nigeria Limted Ajanla Ibadan/Lagos Expressway Ibadan, Oyo state.

- 2016

Laboratory Assistant And Feed Mill/Store Assistant

Internship at Chi farms limited Ajanla as an assistant in the Laboratory and the Feed mill/Store department in a bid to gain extensive practical knowledge relating to academic discipline and others.

Brainer World Limited, Lagos state

- 2015

Administrative and Logistics Head

Supervision of all Administrative and Logistics activities of the Company

Polyfilm Packaging Nigeria Limited. Oluyole Ibadan, Oyo state.

- 2013

Departmental Safety Team Leader and Production Assistant.

Ensring company's safety protocols are adhere to in the department and Assisting the production officer with designated duties

• Visco Yoghurt Alakia Ibadan, Oyo state.

- 2010

Production and safety Assistant

Assisted the production Manager in her activities to ensure proper production of the company's products and Instilling safety consciousness to other employees.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

• Federal University of Technology Akure, (FUTA) Ondo state
Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) in Biology(Storage Technology).

2017

• Olayomi highview, Abayomi Street Eleyele, Ibadan, Oyo state Senior Secondary School Certificate (WASSCE)

2009

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION

Certification in Environmental Health and Safety, level 3 (HSE Level 3) 2019-2020

A Professional course undertaken with the Chateered Institute of Environmental Health and Safety (CIEHS)

Certification in Human Resources Management (In View).

Certification program in process with Novellé training centre

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Team building and Team involvement
- Administrative and Management skill
- Critical and Creative thinking

- A Good Communicator & Conversationist
- Ability to work with little or no supervision

ICT SKILLS

• Microsoft office, Excel, & Power Point

VOLUNTEER ACTIVITIES

CHRISTIAN FELLOWSHIP INTERNATIONAL FUTA CHAPTER(C.f.I FUTA)

- o Final Year Brethren's Co-ordinator (2016-2017)
- o Part-5 Sendoff Committee Chairman (2015)
- Assistant Music Director (2013-2014)
- o Alumni Reunion Committee Chairman (2013)

NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF BIOLOGY STUDENTS FUTA CHAPTER (NABS FUTA)

- Vice Chairman Electoral Committee NABS FUTA (2017)
- o Assistant General Secretary (2013-2014)
- o Class Governor (2012 -2015)

SEMINARS & TRAININGS

· Photography & Videography.

A Seminar and mini-trainning hosted by the verteran and award winning Video producer and cinematographer Stanley Ohikuare (CEO of mighty Jot studios.) In Other to get exposed to another aspect of the entertainment industry, learning the use of cameras and editing software

Cosmetology

A training held by Jalli Multi-Link which helped to improve on knowledge and ideas as regards entrepreneur.

INTERESTS & ACTIVITIES

- · Meeting People
- · Playing scrabble
- Football
- Entrepreneur
- Traveling
- Creating and Listening to good music

PERSONAL DATA

• State of Origin: Oyo
Home Town.: Ibadan
Date of Birth: 8th March
Marital Status: Single
Religion: Christianity

REFEREES

• Available on Request - ""